2308 Armel, Lasalle, Montreal, Quebec, H8N 1L3

Tel.: (438)388-6729 or (647)886-4541 E-mail: david.anderson265@gmail.com

Linkedin: http://ca.linkedin.com/in/danderson2

Website: http://frenziiarts.com		
Summary	Goal-driven professional with expertise in Design, Web Design and Flash animation. 6+ years as a Production Designer who has successfully developed dynamic Graphics for print and Web for companies.	
Areas of Expertise	Software: MS Word, • Excel • Power point • Adobe Photoshop CC, Illustrator CS4 • Flash CC, Dreamweaver 8 • Premiere Pro CC, DVD Studio Pro • Final Cut Pro • After Effects CC Toon Boom 1.2 (2D Animation) • Articulated Storyline Web Languages: HTML5 • Dhtml • CSS3 • XML • Javascript • Action Script 2.0 • WordPress(CMS) Filezilla (FTP) • Audio: Sony Sound Forge • Video compression: Sorenson Squeeze	
Languages	Bilingual: English and French	
Employment Experience	McGill School of Continuing Studies http://www.mcgill.ca/continuingstudies/ Multimedia Courseware Programmer - (August 2014 -2015) Instructor Services and Educational Technologies (ISET) - Department Design and develop online educational content Design and develop templates and applications for use by instructors Assist faculty in creating and using multimedia materials Provide instructors with guidance for the production of online content Evaluate, select and deploy a variety of web based tools and resources Work as part of the School's educational technology team to develop online instructional resources and administrative solutions. Provide technical support for instructors.	

Employment	
Experience	

Mind Geek, Montreal, Canada

http://mindgeek.com/

Ad Developer / Web Designer - (2012-2014)

Playboy.TV department.

- Revamped entire Playboy Radio website
- Delivers static, animated and flash ads to sales team
- Collaborated with sales team leading to the increased of sales by 15%.
- On going optimization of ads and join pages (A/B testing)
- Constantly researching latest trends and technology in the web
- Optimization of Playboy.TV emails to increase sales.

VFM LEONARDO INC, Toronto, Canada http://www.vfmleonardo.com/

2009 - 2011

Multimedia Specialist – (2010-2011) was promoted to marketing department Digital Content Producer – (2009-2010)

Successfully produced over 20 corporate videos which resulted in increase of online activity on company website. Successfully 80 migrated clients to new multimedia platform.

- Collaborated with team to research, analyze and execute assigned projects
- Implement google analytics to website s and web pages
- Produced and monitored banners for multiple campaigns.
- Developed web pages and landing pages, based on management direction and client briefs
- Troubleshoot and resolved interface coding challenges pertaining to browse compatibility
- Produced original and engaging corporate videos online and offline
- Ensure quality control, consistency and integrity of association brands
- Integrated social media tools (Facebook, Youtube, and twitter) with marketing strategies

Employment Experience Cont'd

2007 - 2009

Frenziiarts Media Inc. Montreal, Canada www.frenziiartsmedia.com

Graphic Designer / Web Designer

- Worked closely with Coordinator to design, implement and update a web portal for the Institute for Community Entrepreneurship and Development, John Molson School of Business at Concordia University in Montreal.
- Plan, assign and direct work to contractors
- Update company's website and demo reel
- Produced HTML, CSS, JavaScript and flash pages

2006 - 2006

Graphic Designer and Web Designer

- Successfully managed a creative team of Graphic designers and Web designers.
 Created and developed a website for Stephen Thomas a major spoken word artist.
- Presented mockups layouts for advertisement materials (logo, emails, brochures and websites)
- Produce HTML, CSS, JavaScript coding for landing pages, email templates and websites
- Created dynamic flash ad banners and static ad banners

Nuance, Montreal, Quebec, Canada

2005 - 2006

http://www.nuance.com/ Flash Developer

.
Team received special commendation for tactical demos from Sprint USA.

- Created tactical flash demos for major companies in the telecommunication financial, travel insurance and retail industry
- Produced graphics and audio for the tactical flash demos
- Created streaming flash demos for the web
- Successfully managed and maintained the company website and Intranet pages

2003 - 2004

National Film Board of Canada http://www.nfb.ca/

Special Visual Effects Artist

- Digitally painted frames for short film
- Worked closely with Technical Director and Film Director to create special visual effects for short film

Freelancer 2009 – present

Designer / Web designer

- Designed all ads for print and web for the Taste of the Caribbean Festival
- Produced 30 second commercial spot for Taste of the Caribbean Festival
- Updated and maintained Taste of the Caribbean festival Website

Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts

Major - Film Animation - Concordia University, Montreal, Quebec, Canada – 2005

Diploma in Computer Graphic Design

College Inter – Dec, A.E.C., Montreal, Quebec, Canada – 1999

Certificate in Black and White Photography

Technology Centre, Montreal, Quebec, Canada – 1999